http://www.nbcds.org/privacy-policy

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for https://nbcds.org. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 707-526-6336 or via email craig@nbcds.org.
Become a Member
Upcoming Events
Saturday Evening Waltz Party with Audrey Knuth & Ben Jaber
December 12 @ 7:00 pm - 8:00 pm Audrey and Ben were our first booked talent for the SEWP and they are favorites! This will be their third time playing for us and we couldn’t be more excited. Audrey is a talented fiddler who has electrified dance and concert halls across the US and Europe and now she has partnered with the talented Ben […]
Event Details »
Holiday Saturday Evening Waltz Party with Nils Fredland
December 19 @ 7:00 pm - 8:00 pm Holiday songs, stories and dances with Nils Fredland from  Elixir. Sign up for our emails or Emil sarah@nbcds.org to get the link to join
Event Details »
Saturday Evening Waltz Party with Toss the Possum
December 26 @ 7:00 pm - 8:00 pm We welcome Laura and Rob Zizette back by popular demand! Sign up for our emails to get the link to join or email sarah@nbcds.org
Event Details »
Saturday Evening Waltz Party with Jaqueline Schwab
January 2, 2021 @ 7:00 pm - 8:00 pm We are excited to start 2021 out hosting (sign up for our emails to get the link to join)  Jacqueline Schwab, a folk and classical improvisational pianist who plays “gorgeously spare piano” (The Boston Globe) yet “sounds as if she has an orchestra at her fingertips”
Event Details »
View All Events
Full Calendar »
Never miss a dance! Sign up here for our emails:
Email Address
